https://sunnilandcorp.com/privacy-disclaimers/

Ask The Experts
Contact our experts for questions or advice…FREE!
StateFloridaAlabamaAlaskaArizonaArkansasCaliforniaColoradoConnecticutDelawareGeorgiaHawaiiIdahoIllinoisIndianaIowaKansasKentuckyLouisianaMaineMarylandMassachusettsMichiganMinnesotaMississippiMissouriMontanaNebraskaNevadaNew HampshireNew JerseyNew MexicoNew YorkNorth CarolinaNorth DakotaOhioOklahomaOregonPennsylvaniaRhode IslandSouth CarolinaSouth DakotaTennesseeTexasUtahVermontVirginiaWashingtonWest VirginiaWisconsinWyoming--District of ColumbiaPuerto RicoGuamAmerican SamoaU.S. Virgin IslandsNorthern Mariana Islands
Lawn & Garden ProductsRoofing Products
Yes, subscribe me to your enews tips and info.
Your Information is secure
Privacy & Disclaimers
Privacy Policy
Sunniland Corporation respects your right to the privacy of the personal information you provide us on our websites. To that end, unless you designate otherwise or we state otherwise in this policy or at the time information is collected, any personal information you provide to Sunniland Corporation will be known only to two parties: you and Sunniland Corporation. The following policy is intended to explain how your personal information will be treated as you make use of our sites and their features. Personal information includes your city, state, zip code, click-through activity and any other personal information you may provide here. This policy may change from time to time, so please check back periodically.
Traffic Data
Each time a visitor comes to a Sunniland Corporation website, our servers — like most on the web — collect some basic technical information, including, for example, the visitor’s domain name (e.g., whether the user is logged on from aol.com or whitehouse.gov), referral data (e.g., we record the address of the last URL a user visited prior to clicking through to a Sunniland Corporation website) and browser and platform type (e.g., a Netscape browser on a Macintosh platform).
We also count, track and aggregate the visitor’s activity into our analysis of general traffic flows at our sites (e.g. tracking where traffic comes from, how traffic flows within the Sunniland Corporation sites, etc.). To these ends, we may merge information about visitors and visits into group data, which may then be shared on an aggregated basis with our advertisers; but we will not disclose your individual identity or personally identifiable data without your permission. When we do present aggregated information to outside companies, no one will be able to identify you or contact you.
Use of Sunniland Corporation Cookies
A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive. We use cookies in a limited way to help deliver advertisements, to identify unique browsers that visit us and to track usage throughout our site.
Other companies, which place advertising on our site, also have the ability to assign their cookies to you in a process that Sunniland Corporation does not control. However, cookies cannot be used to identify individuals, only machines, so these advertisers will not know who you are.
E-mail Newsletters
Sunniland Corporation sends a variety of e-mail newsletters to registrants in the Sunniland Corporation Membership program who have requested them. The URLs (web links) in these newsletters contain unique codes that allow Sunniland Corporation to gauge the effectiveness of the newsletters and determine how they are being used. This information is valuable to us in the aggregate, but Sunniland Corporation makes no use of it to track any individual user’s clicks.
Letters to the Editor
Sunniland Corporation asks senders of letters to the editor to include a phone number so we can make an effort to verify their identity should we need to in connection with publication of a letter. We do not retain this information for any other purpose, nor do we sell, trade or otherwise disclose it to third parties.
“Send This Page to a Friend” Feature
Sunniland Corporation offers a “Send this page to a friend” feature, allowing site visitors to send e-mail to friends to inform them about an article or other content they might be interested in reading. In order for this feature to function, we ask for e-mail addresses for the recipient (so we know who to mail the message to) and from the sender (so we can tell the recipient who sent the e-mail). We do not store or save these addresses and you will not receive e-mail or other communications from Sunniland Corporation or its partners as a result of having used this feature.
“Send this page to a friend” is a mail service that individual visitors to Sunniland Corporation make use of to send individual e-mails. While this tool cannot be used to send mass “spam” mailings, Sunniland Corporation has no control over how our visitors use it, and any e-mail sent through it originates with, and is the responsibility of, the sender, not Sunniland Corporation.
Promotion
From time to time, Sunniland Corporation may sponsor sweepstakes, contests or other events, which require the collection, processing and storage of individual contact and demographic information (e.g., your age and state of residence) to be used for the event. Sunniland Corporation may also co-sponsor these events along with other companies, in which case the user’s individual contact and demographic information is likely to be shared with other participating sponsors, who may use this information as they wish. A registrant’s personal contact and demographic information will not be released to any third-party organization other than named sponsors without the user’s consent, and Sunniland Corporation will request that such named sponsors uphold the privacy of the registrants’ information by not distributing or sharing such information with any other businesses or organizations.
Surveys
Sunniland Corporation will from time to time conduct voluntary surveys of visitors to the site to obtain aggregate demographic information about them. Such information may be compiled and shared in the aggregate with advertisers and other third parties, but no personal details will be traceable or associated with specific individuals.
Our Commitment to Children’s Privacy
Protecting the privacy of the very young is important to us. For that reason, we do not collect or maintain information at our websites from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.
Other Disclosure of Personal Information
Sunniland Corporation will not otherwise use or disclose your personal information without your consent except (i) as described in this privacy policy, or (ii) as required by law, court order or as requested by other government or law enforcement authority. This policy does not protect information you post to any on-line bulletin board, chat room, newsgroup or other public forum within our website.
Unsubscribe and Data Removal Policies
Any member may request removal at any time simply by emailing: and referencing your member email address at time of sign up, username and zip code. For confirmation purposes we will send you an email, which you simply reply to, to confirm your removal request.
Other Sites
Sunniland Corporation contains many links to other sites on the web. We cannot control and are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such other websites.
Legal Disclaimer
The Sunniland Corporation name and logo and all related product and service names, design marks and slogans are the trade names, service marks, or trademarks of Sunniland Corporation, and may not be used without the prior written consent of Sunniland Corporation.
These materials are provided by Sunniland Corporation as a service to its readers and may be used for information purposes only. Sunniland Corporation assumes no responsibility for errors or omissions in these materials. Sunniland Corporation makes no commitment to update the information contained herein. Sunniland Corporation makes no, and expressly disclaims any, representations or warranties, express or implied, regarding the Sunniland Corporation website, including without limitation the accuracy, completeness or reliability of text, graphics, links and other items accessed from or via this server or the Internet. No advice or information given by Sunniland Corporation, its affiliates or their respective employees, agents or independent contractors shall create any warranty.
In addition, Sunniland Corporation cannot control and cannot edit content provided by a third party prior to transmission on Sunniland Corporation website, nor can Sunniland Corporation ensure prompt removal of inappropriate or unlawful content after transmission. Third party postings are not reviewed for truth or accuracy and do not represent the opinion, beliefs, or statements of Sunniland Corporation.
Under no circumstances shall Sunniland Corporation or any of its officers, directors, employees, subsidiaries, agents, parents, or affiliates be held liable for any damages, whether incidental, indirect, special or consequential damages and including without limitation, lost revenues or lost profits arising from or in connection with the use or performance of the information on this server or the Internet generally.
Sunniland Corporation retains the copyright in all of the material on these web pages as a collective work under copyright laws. You may not copy, republish, redistribute or exploit in any manner any material from these pages without the express written consent of Sunniland Corporation. You may, however, download copyrighted material for your individual and non-commercial use only.
Who Can I Ask if I Have Any Additional Questions?
If you have any further questions or concerns about the Sunniland Corporation privacy policies and use of personal information, please use our contact form.
Ask The Experts
Contact our experts for questions or advice…FREE!
StateFloridaAlabamaAlaskaArizonaArkansasCaliforniaColoradoConnecticutDelawareGeorgiaHawaiiIdahoIllinoisIndianaIowaKansasKentuckyLouisianaMaineMarylandMassachusettsMichiganMinnesotaMississippiMissouriMontanaNebraskaNevadaNew HampshireNew JerseyNew MexicoNew YorkNorth CarolinaNorth DakotaOhioOklahomaOregonPennsylvaniaRhode IslandSouth CarolinaSouth DakotaTennesseeTexasUtahVermontVirginiaWashingtonWest VirginiaWisconsinWyoming--District of ColumbiaPuerto RicoGuamAmerican SamoaU.S. Virgin IslandsNorthern Mariana Islands
Lawn & Garden ProductsRoofing Products
Yes, subscribe me to your enews tips and info.
Your Information is secure
